Office of Institutional Research and Evaluation Records UA042
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Surveys and reports, 1900 -- 2007; 1965 -- 1999; UA042.001; 56.4 Linear Feet; 139 Digital Object(s)
  - 13 Year Plans, 1999; UA042.001.023.00033 (Box 23)
  - Trends, senior survey, 1999; UA042.001.023.00034 (Box 23)
  - Athletics, senior survey, 2000; UA042.001.023.00035 (Box 23)
  - Career Planning Evaluation, senior survey, 2000; UA042.001.023.00036 (Box 23)
  - Email Communication/Internet Use, senior survey, 2000; UA042.001.023.00037 (Box 23)
  - Engineering, senior survey, 2000; UA042.001.023.00038 (Box 23)
  - Field by salary, senior survey, 2000; UA042.001.023.00039 (Box 23)
  - Graduate School, senior survey, 2000; UA042.001.023.00040 (Box 23)
  - Honorary Degrees, senior survey, 2000; UA042.001.023.00041 (Box 23)
  - International Student Experience, senior survey, 2000; UA042.001.023.00042 (Box 23)
  - Internships, senior survey, 2000; UA042.001.023.00043 (Box 23)
  - Jobs, senior survey, 2000; UA042.001.023.00044 (Box 23)
  - Lernan and Newbauer, senior survey, 2000; UA042.001.023.00045 (Box 23)
  - Major/Minors, senior survey, 2000; UA042.001.023.00046 (Box 23)
  - Major by race, senior survey, 2000; UA042.001.023.00047 (Box 23)
  - Intended major vs. actual major, senior survey, 2000; UA042.001.023.00048 (Box 23)
  - Nominations, senior survey, 2000; UA042.001.023.00049 (Box 23)
  - Peace and Justice Studies, senior survey, 2000; UA042.001.023.00050 (Box 23)
  - Perceptions, senior survey, 2000; UA042.001.023.00051 (Box 23)
  - Preview, senior survey, 2000; UA042.001.023.00052 (Box 23)
  - Student services, senior survey, 2000; UA042.001.023.00053 (Box 23)
  - Summer session, senior survey, 2000; UA042.001.023.00054 (Box 23)
  - TAAP, senior survey, 2000; UA042.001.023.00055 (Box 23)
  - ICAN senior survey, 2000; UA042.001.023.00056 (Box 23)
  - Why/why not, senior survey, 2000; UA042.001.023.00057 (Box 23)
  - HEDS comparative, senior survey, 2000; UA042.001.023.00058 (Box 23)
  - 1999 Dining Services Survey, 2000; UA042.001.023.00059 (Box 23)
  - Best course nominations by department, senior survey, 2000; UA042.001.023.00060 (Box 23)
  - Student perceptions, 1999 senior survey, 2000; UA042.001.023.00061 (Box 23)
  - REAL student report, 2000; UA042.001.023.00062 (Box 23)
  - Comparison of Tufts and peer institutions, 1998 senior survey data, 2000; UA042.001.023.00063 (Box 23)
  - Orientation Survey, 1999 first-year and transfer students, 2000; UA042.001.023.00064 (Box 23)
  - 2000 senior survey, almost final draft, UA042.001.023.00065 (Box 23)
  - Significant impact nominations by department, senior survey, 2000; UA042.001.023.00066 (Box 23)
  - Senior survey preview, 2000; UA042.001.023.00067 (Box 23)
  - Best courses and nominations, senior survey, 2000; UA042.001.023.00068 (Box 23)
  - Win/Loss, 2000; UA042.001.023.00069 (Box 23)
  - Matric, 2000; UA042.001.023.00070 (Box 23)
  - Non Matric, 2000; UA042.001.023.00071 (Box 23)
  - By decision, 2000; UA042.001.023.00072 (Box 23)
  - History, 2000; UA042.001.023.00073 (Box 23)
  - By sex, (1 of 3), 2000; UA042.001.023.00074 (Box 23)
  - By sex, (2 of 3), 2000; UA042.001.023.00075 (Box 23)
  - By sex, (3 of 3), 2000; UA042.001.023.00076 (Box 23)
  - Visit, (1 of 2), 2000; UA042.001.023.00077 (Box 23)
  - Visit, (2 of 2), 2000; UA042.001.023.00078 (Box 23)
  - Colleges, (part 1 of 2), 2000; UA042.001.024.00001 (Box 24)
  - Colleges, (part 2 of 2), 2000; UA042.001.024.00002 (Box 24)
  - Aid, (part 1 of 2), 2000; UA042.001.024.00003 (Box 24)
  - Aid, (part 2 of 2), 2000; UA042.001.024.00004 (Box 24)
  - Race, (part 1 of 2), 2000; UA042.001.024.00005 (Box 24)
  - Race, (part 2 of 2), 2000; UA042.001.024.00006 (Box 24)
  - Comparison of Tufts and Peer Institutions, 1998 Senior Survey Data, 2000; UA042.001.024.00007 (Box 24)
  - Orientation Survey 1999, First Year and Transfer Students, 2000; UA042.001.024.00008 (Box 24)
  - Senior Survey, 2000; UA042.001.024.00009 (Box 24)
  - Significant Impact Nominations by Department, Senior Survey, 2000; UA042.001.024.00010 (Box 24)
  - Senior Survey Preview, 2000; UA042.001.024.00011 (Box 24)
  - Best Courses and Nominations, Senior Survey, 2000; UA042.001.024.00012 (Box 24)
  - Post Graduation Plans for the Class of, 2001; UA042.001.024.00013 (Box 24)
  - Perceptions Report, 2001; UA042.001.024.00014 (Box 24)
  - Senior Survey Data Preview, 2001; UA042.001.024.00015 (Box 24)
  - Best Courses and Nominations, Senior Survey, 2001; UA042.001.024.00016 (Box 24)
  - Nominations for Lerman-Neubauer Prize, 2001; UA042.001.024.00017 (Box 24)
  - Why/Why Not Report, Senior Survey, 2001; UA042.001.024.00018 (Box 24)
  - Alumni Activities Report, Senior Survey, 2001; UA042.001.024.00019 (Box 24)
  - Alumni Activities Report, Senior Survey, 2000; UA042.001.024.00020 (Box 24)
  - Administration and Finance Committee, Executive Session, 1984; UA042.001.025.00001 (Box 25)
  - Beyond the Baccalaureate: Using Admissions Research...: paper by Dawn Terkla, Director, Institutional Research and Planning, 1987; UA042.001.025.00002 (Box 25)
  - Conference Papers on Fund-raising by John Dunn, Vice-President for Planning, Tufts-Educom Data-Sharing Project Data Input Lists, 1985; UA042.001.025.00003 (Box 25)
  - Faculty and Student Reactions to Tufts Portrayal in Guides: Summary, 1985; UA042.001.025.00004 (Box 25)
  - Honors: Info, 1988; UA042.001.025.00005 (Box 25)
  - Accepted Applicants' Matriculation Decisions, 1988; UA042.001.025.00006 (Box 25)
  - Accepted Applicant Study, Final Report, 1991; UA042.001.025.00007 (Box 25)
  - Accepted Applicant Study, Final Report, All Respondents, 1991; UA042.001.025.00008 (Box 25)
  - Accepted Applicant Study, Final Report, By Aid Award, 1991; UA042.001.025.00009 (Box 25)
  - Accepted Applicant Study, Final Report, By College, 1991; UA042.001.025.00010 (Box 25)
  - Accepted Applicant Study, Final Report, By Decision, 1991; UA042.001.025.00011 (Box 25)
  - Accepted Applicant Study, Final Report, By Race, 1991; UA042.001.025.00012 (Box 25)
  - Admissions, 1981 -- 1986; UA042.001.025.00013 (Box 25)
  - Admissions Info. Presented to Trustees, 1988; UA042.001.025.00014 (Box 25)
  - Admissions Reports, 1985 -- 1988; UA042.001.025.00015 (Box 25)
  - Admissions Reports, 11-14, 16-20, 1985 -- 1986; UA042.001.025.00016 (Box 25)
  - Admissions Statistics, 1983 -- 1985; UA042.001.025.00017 (Box 25)
  - Admissions Surveys Background, 1984 -- 1986; UA042.001.025.00018 (Box 25)
  - Boston Campus Housing Survey, 1991; UA042.001.025.00019 (Box 25)
  - Change in Loan Volume Study, 1984; UA042.001.025.00020 (Box 25)
  - Comments: Students Entering Fall, 1987; UA042.001.025.00021 (Box 25)
  - Comments: Survey of Accepted Applicants, 1985; UA042.001.025.00022 (Box 25)
  - Comparisons of Survey Data #1-5, 1981 -- 1982; UA042.001.025.00023 (Box 25)
  - Comparisons of Survey Data #6-10, 1981 -- 1982; UA042.001.025.00024 (Box 25)
  - Decision Stage Competitors, 1986; UA042.001.025.00025 (Box 25)
  - Early Decision Report, 1987; UA042.001.025.00026 (Box 25)
  - Financial Aid and Cost: Report, 1985; UA042.001.025.00027 (Box 25)
  - Financial Aid: Major Sources: Undergrd. Reports, 1987; UA042.001.025.00028 (Box 25)
  - Freshmen Financial Aid Packages, 1987 -- 1988; UA042.001.025.00029 (Box 25)
  - Library User Survey (Arts and Sciences), 1991; UA042.001.025.00030 (Box 25)
  - Library User Survey (Arts and Sciences), 1991; UA042.001.025.00031 (Box 25)
  - Library User Survey (Arts and Sciences), 1991; UA042.001.025.00032 (Box 25)
  - Library User Survey (Arts and Sciences), 1994; UA042.001.025.00033 (Box 25)
  - Library User Survey (Arts and Sciences), 1994 -- 1995; UA042.001.025.00034 (Box 25)
  - Library User Survey: Chemistry Library, 1992; UA042.001.025.00035 (Box 25)
  - Library User Survey: Ginn Library (Fletcher School), 1992; UA042.001.025.00036 (Box 25)
  - Library User Survey: Health Sciences Library (Boston), 1992; UA042.001.025.00037 (Box 25)
  - Library User Survey: Lufkin Engineering Library, 1992; UA042.001.025.00038 (Box 25)
  - Library User Survey: Music Library, 1992; UA042.001.026.00001 (Box 26)
  - Library User Survey: Physics Reading Room, 1992; UA042.001.026.00002 (Box 26)
  - Library User Survey: Tufts University Library, Overall Library Response, 1991 -- 1992; UA042.001.026.00003 (Box 26)
  - Library User Survey: Veterinary School Library, 1992; UA042.001.026.00004 (Box 26)
  - Library User Survey: Wessell Library, 1992; UA042.001.026.00005 (Box 26)
  - Library User Survey: Wessell Library (Library Originals), 1993; UA042.001.026.00006 (Box 26)
  - Minority Enrollment and Student Scholarships, 1985; UA042.001.026.00007 (Box 26)
  - Parents Survey, 1988; UA042.001.026.00008 (Box 26)
  - Resident Life Survey and Report, 1989; UA042.001.026.00009 (Box 26)
  - Senior Survey Data: Evaluation of Majors by Department, 1996; UA042.001.026.00010 (Box 26)
  - Senior Survey Data: Evaluation of Majors by Department, 1996; UA042.001.026.00011 (Box 26)
  - Senior Survey Data: Evaluation of Majors by Department, 1996; UA042.001.026.00012 (Box 26)
  - Senior Survey Data: Evaluation of Majors by Department, 1996; UA042.001.026.00013 (Box 26)
  - Senior Survey Fact Sheet, 1998; UA042.001.026.00014 (Box 26)
  - Senior Survey Questionnaire, 1999; UA042.001.026.00015 (Box 26)
  - Senior Survey Responses, 1998; UA042.001.026.00016 (Box 26)
  - Tufts Open House, 1987; UA042.001.026.00017 (Box 26)
  - Undergraduate Admissions Survey Report (published 1983), UA042.001.026.00018 (Box 26)
  - Undergraduate Admissions: Tables with Comparisons to 1981 Results, 1982; UA042.001.026.00019 (Box 26)
  - Undergraduate Student Changes Over Time, in Comparison to Indicators of Inflation and of Income, 1985; UA042.001.026.00020 (Box 26)
  - Vet School Housing Survey: Preliminary Report, 1985; UA042.001.026.00021 (Box 26)
  - Accepted applicant - New student and non-matriculated surveys, 1994 -- 1995; UA042.001.027.00001; Office of Institutional Research (Box 27)
    Box 2006-01
    - Supporting data, 1994 -- 1995; UA042.001.027.00001.00001; Office of Institutional Research
      Admission
  - Accepted Applicant - New Student and non-matriculated survey, 1996; UA042.001.027.00002; Office of Institutional Research (Box 27)
    - Supporting data, 1996; UA042.001.027.00002.00001; Office of Institutional Research
  - Accepted Applicant - New Student and non-matriculated survey, 1997; UA042.001.027.00003; Office of Institutional Research (Box 27)
    - Supporting data, 1997; UA042.001.027.00003.00001; Office of Institutional Research
      Box 2006-01; See also data from 8 3.5 disks.
  - Accepted Applicant - New Student and non-matriculated survey, 1998; UA042.001.027.00004; Office of Institutional Research (Box 27)
    - Supporting Data, 1998; UA042.001.027.00004.00001; Office of Institutional Research
  - Accepted Applicant - New Student and non-matriculated survey, 1999; UA042.001.027.00005; Office of Institutional Research (Box 27)
    - Supporting data, 1999; UA042.001.027.00005.00001; Office of Institutional Research
  - AAUP Faculty Salary Data and Report, 1996; UA042.001.027.00006; Office of Institutional Research (Box 27)
    - Supporting data, 1996; UA042.001.027.00006.00001; Office of Institutional Research
      Faculty; Salaries; American Association of University Professors
  - AAUP Chronicle, 1996; UA042.001.027.00007; Office of Institutional Research (Box 27)
  - AAUP Faculty Salary Data, 1994 -- 1995; UA042.001.027.00008; Office of Institutional Research (Box 27)
    - Supporting data, 1994; UA042.001.027.00008.00001; Office of Institutional Research
  - AAUP faculty salary data, 1993 -- 1994; UA042.001.027.00009; Office of Institutional Research (Box 27)
  - AAUP faculty salary data, 1995 -- 1996; UA042.001.027.00010; Office of Institutional Research (Box 27)
  - AAUP faculty salary data, 1997 -- 1998; UA042.001.027.00011; Office of Institutional Research (Box 27)
  - AAUP faculty salary data 98-99 and supporting data, 1998 -- 1999; UA042.001.027.00012; Office of Institutional Research (Box 27)
    Box 2006-01; See also data from 1 CD
  - AAUP faculty salary data 98-99 - Wellesley College, 2000 -- 2001; UA042.001.027.00013; Office of Institutional Research (Box 27)
  - AAUP faculty salary data 99-00, 2000; UA042.001.027.00014; Office of Institutional Research (Box 27)
    Box 2006-01; See also data from 1 CD.
    - Supporting data, 2000; UA042.001.027.00014.00001; Office of Institutional Research
      Box 2006-01.
  - AAUP IPEDS survey schedule, 1995; UA042.001.027.00015; Office of Institutional Research (Box 27)
    Box 2006-01; See also data from two 3.5 disks.
    Faculty; Salaries; American Association of University Professors; Integrated Postsecondary Education Data System
    - Supporting data, 1995; UA042.001.027.00015.00001; Office of Institutional Research
  - Academe Magazine, 1995; UA042.001.027.00016 (Box 27)
    Box 2006-01; Bulletin of the American Association of University Professors.
    Faculty; American Association of University Professors
  - Academe Magazine, 1996; UA042.001.027.00017 (Box 27)
  - Academe Magazine, 1903 -- 1997; UA042.001.027.00018 (Box 27)
  - Academe Magazine, 1998; UA042.001.027.00019 (Box 27)
  - Academe Magazine, 1904 -- 1999; UA042.001.027.00020 (Box 27)
  - Accepted applicant trends, 1996 -- 2001; UA042.001.027.00021; Office of Institutional Research (Box 27)
  - Admissions inquiry pilot survey, 1991; UA042.001.027.00022; Office of Institutional Research (Box 27)
  - Admissions inquiry survey, 1995 -- 1996; UA042.001.027.00023; Office of Institutional Research (Box 27)
    Box 2006-01; originally in vinyl folder labeled Inquiry survey 1996; no disk in folder.
  - Admissions inquiry survey, 1999; UA042.001.027.00024; Office of Institutional Research (Box 27)
    Box 2006-01; contains folder labeled "Admissions Inquiry Survey 95,96,97,99"; See also data from 1 CD.
    - Supporting data, 1999; UA042.001.027.00024.00001; Office of Institutional Research
  - Admissions inquiry survey report, 1995; UA042.001.027.00025; Office of Institutional Research (Box 27)
    Box 2006-01; no disks.
  - Admissions selectivity, 1912 -- 1990; UA042.001.027.00026; Office of Institutional Research (Box 27)
  - Admissions inquiry questionaire, 1997; UA042.001.027.00027; Office of Institutional Research (Box 27)
    Box 2006-01; originally in vinyl folder labeled Admissions Inquiry survey 1997; no disks.
  - AICUM Annual report on salaries for United Staes and Massachusetts, 1907 -- 1997; UA042.001.027.00028; Association of Independent Colleges and Universities in MA (Box 27)
    Faculty; Salaries
  - AIR 97-98, 1993 -- 1997; UA042.001.027.00029; Bennett, Claudette; Robinson, J. Gregory (Box 27)
    Box 2006-01; See also data from two 3.5 disk and 1 CD.
    External; Association for Institutional Research
    - AIR 97-98 supporting data, 1993-03-31 -- 1997; UA042.001.027.00029.00001; Bennett, Claudette; Robinson, J. Gregory
  - Data gathered from accepted applicant survey on African American students, 1995; UA042.001.027.00030; Office of Institutional Research (Box 27)
    Admission; African Americans
  - Faculty salaries - Chronicle, 1904 -- 1999; UA042.001.027.00031 (Box 27)
  - Financial aid package and matriculation decisions accepted applicants, 1905 -- 1997; UA042.001.027.00032; Office of Institutional Research (Box 27)
    Admission; Financial Aid
  - Parents survey, 1995; UA042.001.027.00033; Terkla, Dawn Geronimo; Armstong, Kelli J. (Box 27)
    Box 2006-01; See also three 3.5 disks and CD; contains three sub-folders
    Admission; Parents
    - Supporting documentation, 1995; UA042.001.027.00033.00001; Terkla, Dawn Geronimo; Armstong, Kelli J.
  - Impact of financial aid on student satisfaction, 1990; UA042.001.027.00034; Terkla, Dawn Geronimo; Pagano, Marian F. (Box 27)
    Financial Aid; External
  - Tufts University admission inquiry, 1998; UA042.001.027.00035; Office of Institutional Research (Box 27)
  - TUSDM Classes of 1991 and 1994 Alumni/alumnae survey report, 1910 -- 1996; UA042.001.027.00036; Office of Institutional Research (Box 27)
    Box 2006-01; contains three sub-folders
    Alumni and alumnae; School of Dental Medicine
  - Admissions-marketing trip survey, 1908 -- 1996; UA042.001.027.00037; Office of Institutional Research (Box 27)
    Box 2006-02
  - Arts and Sciences Library Spring User Survey, 1995; UA042.001.027.00038; Office of Institutional Research (Box 27)
    Libraries; Arts and Sciences; User
    - Supporting Data, 1995; UA042.001.027.00038.00001; Office of Institutional Research
  - Arts and Sciences Library User Survey, 1991; UA042.001.027.00039; Office of Institutional Research (Box 27)
  - Career planning for underclassmen: Early intervention Sophomore vs. Senior [1 of 2], 1996; UA042.001.027.00040; Terkla, Dawn Geronimo; Markwardt, Marcia L. (Box 27)
    Undergraduates; Career development
  - Career planning for underclassmen: Early intervention Sophomore vs. Senior [2 of 2], 1996; UA042.001.027.00041; Terkla, Dawn Geronimo; Markwardt, Marcia L. (Box 27)
  - Council of Ivy Presidents-Career Choice, 1995; UA042.001.027.00042 (Box 27)
  - Admissions inquiries, frequencies, and questionaires, 1999 -- 2000; UA042.001.028.00001; Office of Institutional Research (Box 28)
    Also contains data from one 3.5 floppy disk
    - Supporting Data, 1999 -- 2000; UA042.001.028.00001.00001; Office of Institutional Research
  - Biology Hughes Grant Interview Protocol, 1985 -- 1995; UA042.001.028.00002 (Box 28)
  - CIRP Questionnaires, 1989; UA042.001.028.00003 (Box 28)
    contains two folders - CIRP and CIRP 1989 Questionnaires
  - CIRP Freshman Survey, 1986; UA042.001.028.00004 (Box 28)
  - Civic Education Foundation, 1987 -- 1988; UA042.001.028.00005 (Box 28)
  - Department Based Audit of Undergraduate Instruction, 1985 -- 1995; UA042.001.028.00006 (Box 28)
  - Enrollment Study Raw Data, 1991 -- 1998; UA042.001.028.00007 (Box 28)
  - Enrollment Study Raw Data, 1996 -- 1998; UA042.001.028.00008 (Box 28)
  - Exec Summary Yr 1 Bio Surveys, 1996; UA042.001.028.00009 (Box 28)
  - Fletcher Enrolled, 1999; UA042.001.028.00010 (Box 28)
    also includes data extracted from 3.5 in floppy disk
    - Fletcher Enrolled-supporting data from disk, 1999; UA042.001.028.00010.00001
      Transfer file from 3.5 floppy disk labeled 'Fletcher Both'
  - Fletcher Matric, 1999; UA042.001.028.00011 (Box 28)
    contains two folders: Fletcher Enrolled '99 (II) and Fletcher Enrolled '99 (III)
  - Hughes Grant Interview Log and Executive Summary, 1994 -- 1995; UA042.001.028.00012 (Box 28)
  - Final - Minority Student Study Oct. 8, 1985; UA042.001.028.00013 (Box 28)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1997; UA042.001.028.00014 (Box 28)
  - Pre Major Advising LA Data, 1999; UA042.001.028.00015 (Box 28)
  - Tufts Bioscience Summer Research Program Dept. of Biology, 1997; UA042.001.028.00016 (Box 28)
  - Tufts Bioscience Summer Research Program Dept. of Biology, 1998; UA042.001.028.00017 (Box 28)
  - Year 1 Biology Survey, 1995 -- 1996; UA042.001.028.00018 (Box 28)
  - Year 2 Biology Survey, 1996 -- 1997; UA042.001.028.00019 (Box 28)
  - Year 3 Biology Survey, 1997 -- 1998; UA042.001.028.00020 (Box 28)
  - Academic Technology Focus Group, 2001; UA042.001.028.00021 (Box 28)
  - Accreditation, 2001 -- 2003; UA042.001.028.00022 (Box 28)
  - CIHE Standards for Accreditation, 1999; UA042.001.028.00023 (Box 28)
  - Enrollment Study Year [1 of 4], 1991 -- 1992; UA042.001.028.00024 (Box 28)
  - Enrollment Study Year [2 of 4], 1991 -- 1992; UA042.001.028.00025 (Box 28)
  - Enrollment Study Year [3 of 4], 1991 -- 1992; UA042.001.028.00026 (Box 28)
  - Enrollment Study [4 of 4], 1991 -- 1992; UA042.001.028.00027 (Box 28)
  - Enrollment Trends Social Sciences '91-'03, 1999 -- 2003; UA042.001.028.00028 (Box 28)
  - Fletcher Career Services Survey, 2004; UA042.001.028.00029 (Box 28)
  - Major Advising for Engineering [Binder], 1995; UA042.001.028.00030 (Box 28)
    also contains information extracted from three 3.5 inch floppy disks
    - Major Advising for Engineering [Binder] data extracted from 3 disks, 1995; UA042.001.028.00030.00001
      Transfer files from three disks.
  - National Board Analysis Outcomes Assessment, 2004; UA042.001.028.00031 (Box 28)
  - Pre-Major Advising, 1995; UA042.001.028.00032 (Box 28)
    taken from binder originally labeled: Pre-Major Advising 1995; contains information extracted from two 3.5 inch floppy disks
    - Pre-Major Advising transfer file data, 1995; UA042.001.028.00032.00001
      Transfer data extracted from three 3.5 inch floppy disks
  - Pre-Major Advising, 1997; UA042.001.028.00033 (Box 28)
    Originally contained in two folders labeled: Advising 1997 Liberal Arts and Advising 1997 Engineering; contains information extracted from one CD and six 3.5 inch floppy disks
    - Pre-Major Advising transfer file data, 1997; UA042.001.028.00033.00001
      Transfer files extracted from six 3.5 inch floppy disks and one CD
  - Sophomore survey, 2001 -- 2004; UA042.001.029.00001; Office of Institutional Research (Box 29)
    - Sophomore Survey, 2001 -- 2004; UA042.001.029.00001.00001; Office of Institutional Research
    - Sophomore Survey 2004, 2001 -- 2004; UA042.001.029.00001.00002; Office of Institutional Research
    - Sophomore Survey 1, 2004; UA042.001.029.00001.00003; Office of Institutional Research
      Original file name: appendices for sophomore survey 2004.xls, sophomore experience survey 2004-final-cleaned data for appendices.xls
  - Senior survey (book one of two) [1 of 3], 2004; UA042.001.029.00002; Office of Institutional Research (Box 29)
    - SS HEDS Comparison, 2004; UA042.001.029.00002.00001; Office of Institutional Research
  - Senior survey (book one of two) [2 of 3], 2004; UA042.001.029.00003; Office of Institutional Research (Box 29)
  - Senior survey (book one of two) [3 of 3], 2004; UA042.001.029.00004; Office of Institutional Research (Box 29)
  - Senior survey (book two of two) [1 of 3], 2004; UA042.001.029.00005; Office of Institutional Research (Box 29)
  - Senior survey (book two of two) [2 of 3], 2003 -- 2004; UA042.001.029.00006; Office of Institutional Research (Box 29)
    - Senior Survey Reports, 2004; UA042.001.029.00006.00001; Office of Institutional Research
    - Senior Survey Reports, 2003; UA042.001.029.00006.00002; Office of Institutional Research
  - Senior survey (book two of two) [3 of 3], 2004; UA042.001.029.00007; Office of Institutional Research (Box 29)
  - Senior survey: Detail reports, 2004; UA042.001.029.00008; Office of Institutional Research (Box 29)
    This folder is now empty. The former contents were digital and have now been transferred to the Dark Archive.
    - Senior Survey Detail Reports, 2004; UA042.001.029.00008.00001; Office of Institutional Research
  - Major advising report [1 of 3], 2004; UA042.001.029.00009; Office of Institutional Research (Box 29)
  - Major advising report [2 of 3], 2004; UA042.001.029.00010; Office of Institutional Research (Box 29)
  - Major advising report [3 of 3], 2004; UA042.001.029.00011; Office of Institutional Research (Box 29)
  - Admissions Statistics - Undergraduate ASE, 1993 -- 2006; UA042.001.029.00012; Office of Institutional Research (Box 29)
  - Admissions Statistics - Grad and prof, 1993 -- 2006; UA042.001.029.00013; Office of Institutional Research (Box 29)
  - Analysis by degree, 1992 -- 2005; UA042.001.029.00014; Office of Institutional Research (Box 29)
  - Char. entering - Grad and prof, 1991 -- 2006; UA042.001.029.00015; Office of Institutional Research (Box 29)
  - Char. entering - Ugrad, 1991 -- 2006; UA042.001.029.00016; Office of Institutional Research (Box 29)
  - Class of 1965 survey, 2005; UA042.001.029.00017; Office of Institutional Research (Box 29)
  - Enrollment - special statistics, 1991 -- 2006; UA042.001.029.00018; Office of Institutional Research (Box 29)